welcome to your very first beginning
ยินดีต้อนรับสู่จุดเริ่มต้นแรกของคุณ
tutorial on CSS and this is part of our
กวดวิชาเกี่ยวกับ CSS และนี่เป็นส่วนหนึ่งของเรา
ongoing web development series now if
ชุดพัฒนาเว็บต่อเนื่องในขณะนี้ถ้า
you do not have a solid understanding of
คุณไม่มีความเข้าใจที่มั่นคง
HTML you should go to my channel page
HTML ที่คุณควรไปที่หน้าช่องของฉัน
and go through the HTML for beginners
และผ่าน HTML สำหรับผู้เริ่มต้น
tutorial set that's kind of a
ชุดกวดวิชาที่เป็น
prerequisite now if you already know
จำเป็นถ้าตอนนี้คุณรู้แล้ว
HTML and you feel you don't need that
HTML และคุณรู้สึกว่าคุณไม่จำเป็นต้องใช้
that's fine but if you don't know
ไม่เป็นไร แต่ถ้าคุณไม่รู้จัก
anything about HTML I strongly recommend
อะไรเกี่ยวกับ HTML ฉันขอแนะนำ
that you go ahead and take that series
ที่คุณไปข้างหน้าและใช้ชุดที่
because an understanding of HTML is
เพราะความเข้าใจเรื่อง HTML คือ
really crucial to using CSS now as a
สิ่งสำคัญมากในการใช้ CSS ในขณะนี้คือ a
note we will also be introducing some
ทราบเรายังจะแนะนำบางส่วน
new HTML elements in this series and the
องค์ประกอบ HTML ใหม่ในชุดนี้และ
reason is they go hand-in-hand together
เหตุผลที่พวกเขาไปจับมือกัน
so it didn't make sense to discuss those
ดังนั้นจึงไม่มีเหตุผลที่จะพูดถึงเรื่องเหล่านั้น
in the HTML for beginners because they
ใน HTML สำหรับผู้เริ่มต้นเนื่องจากพวกเขา
really work hand in hand with CSS in
จริงๆทำงานจับมือกับ CSS ได้
terms of what you will need we're just
ข้อกำหนดในสิ่งที่คุณต้องการเราเป็นเพียง
gonna use notepad for now just like we
จะใช้ Notepad ในตอนนี้เช่นเดียวกับเรา
did in the HTML for beginners series now
ใน HTML สำหรับผู้เริ่มต้นใช้งานได้ทันที
eventually we'll use an editor but for
ในที่สุดเราจะใช้โปรแกรมแก้ไข แต่สำหรับ
now we just need no pen okay so what is
ตอนนี้เราแค่ต้องการปากกาไม่ได้แล้วล่ะ
CSS well here's the dictionary version
CSS ดีนี่คือเวอร์ชันพจนานุกรม
CSS stands for cascading style sheets it
CSS ย่อมาจาก cascading style sheets นั่นเอง